<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Xianglin Huang</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Xianglin Huang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>You</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:13:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xhuangacct.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Resume</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/cv/myresume/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:13:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/cv/myresume/</guid><description>XIANGLIN HUANG 12030 Chase Crossing Circle North Bethesda, MD 20852 xhuangacct@gmail.com (667)786-9532
RESEARCH INTERESTS Accounting Disclosure, Accounting Data Visualization, Accounting’s Role in Supply Chain
EDUCATION BALTIMORE CITY COMMUNITY COLLEGE, Baltimore, MD, Accounting, 2022 to Present GPA 4.0/4.0 Courses: ACCT 221, ACCT 222, ECO 201, BUAD 100, SP 101, etc.
UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY OF CHINA, Anhui, China M.S., Public Administration, 2014 B.S., Business Administration, 2011 B.A., Communication, 2011
PUBLICATION Huang, Xianglin and Zhu,Xiuli.</description></item><item><title>How I Learned to Build My Site</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/myfirstpost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/myfirstpost/</guid><description>Jumpstart
Key takeaways: set github account with shh keys Make sure git push can be successfully excuted through command line.
create local directory Rather than &amp;ldquo;mkdir&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;git clone&amp;rdquo; an empty repository to make a new directory which has the same name.
Thinking * Question 1: How to set my github account so that - Answer: SSH key. * Question 2: How to set a local directory so that it can easily connect a github repository.</description></item><item><title>Persuasive Speech: Why Should We Take a Break</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/persuasivespeech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 16:08:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/persuasivespeech/</guid><description>Persuasive Speech: Why should we take a break Xianglin Huang - SP 101 - 1067 General purpose: To persuade
Specific purpose: To convince my audience to take a break
INTRODUCTION Good morning, Professor Boas, good morning, class. My name is Xianglin Huang. I’m here to persuade you to take a break.
Last week, I cut my thumb hard while I was in the kitchen. I was literally shocked because normally I don’t do that and it happened when I actually focused my eyesight on my fingers.</description></item><item><title>Infomative Speech: Confirmation Bias</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/infomativespeech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 15:50:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/infomativespeech/</guid><description>INFORMATIVE SPEECH: CONFIRMATION BIAS Xianglin Huang - SP 101 - 1067 General purpose: To inform my audience
Specific purpose: To explain what is confirmation bias and how to avoid it
INTRODUCTION Imagine you are a married man and your wife believes you are cheating on her. When you try to explain, she says you are just trying to conceal. When you try to make her feel better, she says you do all those things because you feel guilty.</description></item><item><title>Assignment: Reviews on Five Accounting Articles</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/acct-221-wriiten-assignment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 16:32:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/acct-221-wriiten-assignment/</guid><description>“Tech and automation innovation in tax and accounting,” By Jody Padar, June 15, 2022, https://www.accountingtoday.com/opinion/tech-and-automaton-innovation-in-tax-and-accounting
“Using Data Visualization To Help Uncover Fraud,” By Kathleen M. Bakarich, June 2022, https://www.cpajournal.com/2022/06/06/using-data-visualization-to-help-uncover-fraud/
“Department of Labor Position on Cryptocurrency Investment in 401(k) Plans,” By Sheldon M. Geller, June 2022, https://www.cpajournal.com/2022/06/15/department-of-labor-position-on-cryptocurrency-investment-in-401k-plans/
“What every CPA should know about disrupted supply chains,” By Andrew Kenney, May 12, 2022, https://www.journalofaccountancy.com/news/2022/may/what-every-cpa-should-know-about-disrupted-supply-chains.html
“5 steps to managing client expectations,” By Anita Dennis, May 13, 2022, https://www.</description></item><item><title>Assignment: How Business Use Information</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/buad100-writing-research-assignment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 16:19:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/buad100-writing-research-assignment/</guid><description>How Business Use Information Xianglin Huang The value of a business is typically indicated by its assets—property, plants, equipment, inventory and even human resources (Lumen Learning et al). However, information is arguably the most essential component for businesses to remain competitive. It is generally accepted that the explosion of technology has led the world into the Information Age. The utilization of information not only means that businesses should stay in control of their data, but also means they should keep up to date with the development of technology.</description></item><item><title>Paper: Comparison of Aristotle's and Confucius' Doctrines of the Mean</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/phi101-analysispaper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 14:07:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/phi101-analysispaper/</guid><description>Comparison of Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s and Confucius&amp;rsquo; Doctrines of the Mean Introduction Aristotle (384 BC - 322 BC) and Confucius (551 BC - 479 BC) were both great philosophers of their eras. Coincidentally, the two philosophers developed their doctrines of the Mean in similar or different settings. Aristotle’s virtuous Mean is introduced in his book Nicomachean Ethics(Book II),while Confucius&amp;rsquo;s doctrine of the Mean is introduced in an ancient Chinese book called The doctrine of the mean, written by Zisi, who was Confucius’s grandson.</description></item><item><title>Statistics Project: How Long Can You Focus on Study at Home</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/mat107-timeproject-part01/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 10:35:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/mat107-timeproject-part01/</guid><description>MAT107 Intro to Statistics Project
Name Xianglin Huang due by 4/9/2022 .
STEP 1: Data Collection
How many minutes do you sit down and work with dedicated concentration on your homework without interruption? Look at the time when you start. If you stop working to look at a phone message, take a call or a break, stop the time and write it down. If you listen to music while you study, stop the time when you change the music station, find another song or anything other than making progress on your homework.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 17:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi! My name is Xianglin Huang. I grew up in an honest and humble Chinese peasantry family in Huanggang, China. My father is an honest and humble peasant electrician. He worked diligently in his profession for over thirty-three years. Influenced by him, I made good efforts in study and got admitted in the University of Science and Technology of China (USTC) when I was 18. Then I spent six years on my study and one year voluntarily teaching in a rural middle school in the west of China.</description></item></channel></rss>