<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Xianglin Huang</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Xianglin Huang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>You</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 18:20:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>11 14 2022</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/11-14-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 18:20:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/11-14-2022/</guid><description>acquisition of plant asset
historical cost is objective historical cost consists of all expenditures ordinaru and necessary to acquire an asset and make it ready for its intended use changes in a plant asset&amp;rsquo;s fair value subsequent to acquisition are generally ignored companies should not anticipate gains, but should recognize gains only if/ when a plant asset is sold major sub-classifications land/building/ready for use/lease/
cost of land costs typically include:</description></item><item><title>TOEFL Speaking Practice</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-05-2022-toefl-speaking-concepts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 14:38:53 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-05-2022-toefl-speaking-concepts/</guid><description>Question 1:
If I could have any job, I would choose to be a writer. This is because I enjoy writing, reading, and being able to stay with my family when I work. First, I enjoy writing. I love writing about different type of materials, like a story, a news or a principle. Whenever I write, I feel peaceful and calm. Writing is a kind of therapy of my soul.</description></item><item><title>TOEFL Speaking Ideas</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-02-2022-toefl-speaking-practice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 20:48:50 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-02-2022-toefl-speaking-practice/</guid><description>Introduction practice:
Question 1:
If I could have any job, I would choose to be a writer. This is because I enjoy telling stories and experiencing things deeply and making people feel more alive.
If I could have any job, I would choose to be an icecream truck driver. I think this because it is a lifelong dream of me and I enjoy seeing others&amp;rsquo; happy when they get icecreams. Question 2:</description></item><item><title>Accounting Programs Interested</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-02-2022-programs-interested/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:57:15 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/10-02-2022-programs-interested/</guid><description>UMD College Park
GWU
Penn State
Wharton</description></item><item><title>Assignment: Financial Analysis of Amazon.com</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/9-28-2022-accounting-analysis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 15:02:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/9-28-2022-accounting-analysis/</guid><description>Name: Xianglin Huang Course: ACCT 221 Semester: Summer II, 2022 What is the name of your company? (3pts) Amazon.com, Inc. What are the letters they use when trading in the stock market? (3pts) AMZN What is their principal activity? (3pts) Retail is Amazon&amp;rsquo;s principal activity, including e-commerce websites and physical stores (Johnston, 2022). Amazon.com provides a platform for sellers and buyers to easily complete their deals. Additionally, Amazon sells its own brands.</description></item><item><title>How to Keep Track on Latest Accounting Articles</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/2022-09-26-how-to-get-familiar-with-accounting-field/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 15:59:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/2022-09-26-how-to-get-familiar-with-accounting-field/</guid><description>If you decide to dig into Accounting, it is very important to keep reading and taking notes of the latest accounting articles from top journals in the field. According to https://academic-accelerator.com/, the top accounting journals include:
Journal of Accounting and Economics(ISSN:0165-4101) British Accounting Review(ISSN:0890-8389 1095-8347) International Journal of Accounting Information Systems(ISSN:1467-0895) Journal of Accounting Research(ISSN:0021-8456 1475-679X) Accounting Review(ISSN:0001-4826) You can access the journals through college library. For example: Montgomery College. Find library homepage on the college website.</description></item><item><title>How I Learned to Build My Site</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/myfirstpost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/myfirstpost/</guid><description>Jumpstart
Key takeaways: set github account with shh keys Make sure git push can be successfully excuted through command line.
create local directory Rather than &amp;ldquo;mkdir&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;git clone&amp;rdquo; an empty repository to make a new directory which has the same name.
Thinking * Question 1: How to set my github account so that - Answer: SSH key. * Question 2: How to set a local directory so that it can easily connect a github repository.</description></item><item><title>Persuasive Speech: Why Should We Take a Break</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/persuasivespeech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 16:08:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/persuasivespeech/</guid><description>Persuasive Speech: Why should we take a break Xianglin Huang - SP 101 - 1067 General purpose: To persuade
Specific purpose: To convince my audience to take a break
INTRODUCTION Good morning, Professor Boas, good morning, class. My name is Xianglin Huang. I’m here to persuade you to take a break.
Last week, I cut my thumb hard while I was in the kitchen. I was literally shocked because normally I don’t do that and it happened when I actually focused my eyesight on my fingers.</description></item><item><title>Infomative Speech: Confirmation Bias</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/infomativespeech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 15:50:36 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/infomativespeech/</guid><description>INFORMATIVE SPEECH: CONFIRMATION BIAS Xianglin Huang - SP 101 - 1067 General purpose: To inform my audience
Specific purpose: To explain what is confirmation bias and how to avoid it
INTRODUCTION Imagine you are a married man and your wife believes you are cheating on her. When you try to explain, she says you are just trying to conceal. When you try to make her feel better, she says you do all those things because you feel guilty.</description></item><item><title>Assignment: Reviews on Five Accounting Articles</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/acct-221-wriiten-assignment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 16:32:35 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/acct-221-wriiten-assignment/</guid><description>“Tech and automation innovation in tax and accounting,” By Jody Padar, June 15, 2022, https://www.accountingtoday.com/opinion/tech-and-automaton-innovation-in-tax-and-accounting
“Using Data Visualization To Help Uncover Fraud,” By Kathleen M. Bakarich, June 2022, https://www.cpajournal.com/2022/06/06/using-data-visualization-to-help-uncover-fraud/
“Department of Labor Position on Cryptocurrency Investment in 401(k) Plans,” By Sheldon M. Geller, June 2022, https://www.cpajournal.com/2022/06/15/department-of-labor-position-on-cryptocurrency-investment-in-401k-plans/
“What every CPA should know about disrupted supply chains,” By Andrew Kenney, May 12, 2022, https://www.journalofaccountancy.com/news/2022/may/what-every-cpa-should-know-about-disrupted-supply-chains.html
“5 steps to managing client expectations,” By Anita Dennis, May 13, 2022, https://www.</description></item><item><title>Assignment: How Business Use Information</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/buad100-writing-research-assignment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 16:19:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/buad100-writing-research-assignment/</guid><description>How Business Use Information Xianglin Huang The value of a business is typically indicated by its assets—property, plants, equipment, inventory and even human resources (Lumen Learning et al). However, information is arguably the most essential component for businesses to remain competitive. It is generally accepted that the explosion of technology has led the world into the Information Age. The utilization of information not only means that businesses should stay in control of their data, but also means they should keep up to date with the development of technology.</description></item><item><title>Paper: Comparison of Aristotle's and Confucius' Doctrines of the Mean</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/phi101-analysispaper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 14:07:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/phi101-analysispaper/</guid><description>Comparison of Aristotle&amp;rsquo;s and Confucius&amp;rsquo; Doctrines of the Mean Introduction Aristotle (384 BC - 322 BC) and Confucius (551 BC - 479 BC) were both great philosophers of their eras. Coincidentally, the two philosophers developed their doctrines of the Mean in similar or different settings. Aristotle’s virtuous Mean is introduced in his book Nicomachean Ethics(Book II),while Confucius&amp;rsquo;s doctrine of the Mean is introduced in an ancient Chinese book called The doctrine of the mean, written by Zisi, who was Confucius’s grandson.</description></item><item><title>Statistics Project: How Long Can You Focus on Study at Home</title><link>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/mat107-timeproject-part01/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 10:35:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://xhuangacct.github.io/posts/mat107-timeproject-part01/</guid><description>MAT107 Intro to Statistics Project
Name Xianglin Huang due by 4/9/2022 .
STEP 1: Data Collection
How many minutes do you sit down and work with dedicated concentration on your homework without interruption? Look at the time when you start. If you stop working to look at a phone message, take a call or a break, stop the time and write it down. If you listen to music while you study, stop the time when you change the music station, find another song or anything other than making progress on your homework.</description></item></channel></rss>